I will call to order the regular scheduled meeting of the City Council for Tuesday, March 31st, 2026.
Item number 2A is consideration to take action with respect to Resolution CC-2026-06,
which is the same resolution we just passed on MSUA, but on the City Council side.
Motion approved.
2B, appoint Shannon Biggs and Hugh Murray to the Ottawa County Emergency Communications Center Resource Board.
Item number 2C, remove the issued weapon and badge from inventory for retiring Police Department employee Detective Kelly Johnson.
I make a motion to approve.
Second.
Cool.
Parson.
Aye.
Easton.
Jones.
Aye.
Barnes.
Item 3, adjournment.
Motion.
Second.